http://www.lexcycle.com/privacy

Home Privacy Policy
Please note that the practices of Lexcycle, Inc., its affiliates, and agents ("Lexcycle"), with respect to data collected and used by Lexcycle in connection with this website and all other Lexcycle.com websites of Lexcycle, Inc. and its affiliates with links to this policy (collectively, the “Site”) and Lexcycle products and services available or enabled via the Site (“Products and Services”), are governed by this online privacy policy (“Privacy Policy”) as amended from time to time, and not the privacy policy in effect at the time the data was collected. Please regularly review our Privacy Policy. If you have objections to the Privacy Policy, you should immediately discontinue use of the Site and the Products and Services enabled by the Site and follow the procedure described in the section entitled "Updating your personal information and privacy preferences".
This Privacy Policy does not govern privacy practices associated with offline activities, websites other than the Site, or Products and Services not available or enabled via the Site, except as expressly set forth in the section entitled "Data not collected on this Site." Notwithstanding the foregoing, to the extent that any terms of the Privacy Policy conflict with the terms of an existing written (including electronic) agreement between you and Lexcycle regarding the use of specific areas of the Site or specific Products and Services (including Product- and Service-specific licenses, terms of use, or privacy disclosures) (collectively, “Product Agreements”), the terms of the Product Agreements shall govern.
Lexcycle adheres to the European Union Safe Harbor principles as set forth by the United States Department of Commerce regarding the collection, use, and retention of personal information covered by the Privacy Policy from the European Union.
The Site and the Products and Services are intended for adult audiences, and Lexcycle does not knowingly collect any personal information from anyone under 13 years of age.
Changes in Privacy Policy
All personal information ("personal information" is defined as any information that identifies or can be used to identify the person to whom such information pertains) that we collect and maintain will be subject to this Privacy Policy, as amended from time to time. Lexcycle may change the Privacy Policy from time to time at its sole discretion and will provide notice of changes in the Privacy Policy and on the home page of Lexcycle.com. If as the result of such changes you want to alter the ways in which Lexcycle is allowed to use your personal information, you can do so by following the procedure described in the section entitled “Updating your personal information and privacy preferences.” You will be deemed to have been made aware of, and will be subject to, the changes to the Privacy Policy after such notice has been posted with the following exception: if at the time you provide personal information to Lexcycle you limit how such information will be used to communicate with you, either by Lexcycle or by third parties, Lexcycle will not change your preference in this regard without your express consent. However, if Lexcycle sells assets (or the assets of a division or subsidiary) to another entity, or Lexcycle (or a division or subsidiary) is acquired by or merged with another entity, you agree that Lexcycle may provide to such entity customer information that is related to that part of our business that was sold to or merged with the other entity without obtaining your further consent, but Lexcycle will provide notice of such asset sales, acquisitions, or mergers on this Site.
Entities collecting personal information
Personal information on this Site is collected on behalf of Lexcycle by Lexcycle, Inc., who is responsible for this site.
The Site contains links to other sites at which personal information is collected. In such instances, unless expressly provided to the contrary, the collection and use of your personal information will be governed by the privacy policy applicable to that site. That privacy policy should identify the entity that is collecting your personal information.
Updating your personal information and privacy preferences
You have the right to access and correct your personal information and privacy preferences at any time. With respect to Registration Information (as defined in the section entitled "Protection of your personal information"), this may be accomplished by linking to your account at Edit Your Account, where you can view and make changes to your personal information.
You may also access and correct your personal information and privacy preferences (such as whether you wish to receive promotional communications) by writing Lexcycle at:
Lexcycle, Inc.
Attn: Change of Address/Privacy
1412 SE 41st Ave
Portland, OR 97214
USA
Personal information submitted through this Site or in connection with the Products and Servicesthat is not Registration Information is not accessible online.
To access and/or correct such information and privacy preferences (such as whether you wish to receive promotional communications), you may write Lexcycle at:
Lexcycle, Inc.
Privacy Officer/Customer Information
1412 SE 41st Ave
Portland, OR 97214
USA
All users may also email: privacy-officer@lexcycle.com
In your correspondence, please indicate with as much detail as possible the location on this Site or otherwise where you provided your personal information. You may expect a response within 30 days.For information submitted in connection with Products and Services, you may also follow instructions included or referenced within such Product and Service to access or correct the information.
Collection of personal information
As a visitor to this Site, you can engage in many activities without providing any personal information. In connection with other activities, such as utilizing online or hosted Products and Services, Lexcycle may ask you to provide certain information about yourself by filling out and submitting a form. It is optional for you to engage in these activities. If you elect to engage in these activities, however, Lexcycle may ask that you provide personal information, such as your first and last name, mailing address (including ZIP code), country of residence, e-mail address, employer, job title and department, telephone and facsimile numbers, and other personal information. When ordering Products and Services via the Site, you may be asked to provide a credit card number. Depending upon the activity, some of the information that we ask you to provide is identified as mandatory and some as voluntary. If you do not provide the mandatory data with respect to a particular activity, you will not be able to engage in that activity.
Similarly, if you wish to delete your information (pursuant to the mechanism set forth in “Updating your personal information and privacy preferences”) that is mandatory, you will no longer be able to engage in a particular activity.
When you use the Site and the Products and Services, Lexcycle may also collect certain information about your computer to facilitate and evaluate your use of the Site and the Products and Services. For example, we may log environmental variables, such as browser type, operating system, CPU speed, referring or exit webpages, and the Internet Protocol (IP) address of your computer.
Lexcycle also uses such information to measure traffic patterns on the Site and usage of the Products and Services. We do not match such information with any other information held by Lexcycle unless we have your consent.
By using this Site and the Products and Services, you agree and acknowledge that personal information collected through the Site or in connection with the Products and Services may be transferred across national boundaries and stored and processed in any of the countries around the world in which Lexcycle maintains offices, including the United States. You also acknowledge that in certain countries or with respect to certain activities, the collection, transfer, storage, and processing of your information may be undertaken by trusted third parties. Such third parties are bound by contract with Lexcycle not to use your personal information for their own purposes or provide it to any third parties. One instance where this could occur is in conjunction with framed pages in which the URL for the pages is not visible, and the pages are hosted for Lexcycle by such third parties.
For example, on the sign up pages for some newsletters, the pages may be hosted by a third party vendor, but appear to be Lexcycle.com pages and are governed by the Lexcycle privacy policy.
Lexcycle has established relationships with various service providers whose services are available to you from the Site, from websites that are linked to the Site, or in connection with the Products and Services. Typically, these providers offer services that Lexcycle customers might find useful, such as those that can be used in conjunction with Products and Services. In order to use those providers’ services, you may be required to provide personal information to the providers. Unless expressly provided to the contrary, personal information that you provide while you are visiting a provider's website will be subject to the privacy policy posted on that site, and personal information that you provide while on the Site will be subject to this Privacy Policy.
In order to reduce errors in our database, authenticate our users, prevent abuse of our Site and the Products and Services, and provide more consistent, relevant experiences to our users,
we may on occasion supplement the personal information you submit to us with information from third-party sources. For example, if permitted under applicable law, we may supplement your Registration Information with address information provided by the U.S. Postal Service to qualify your information and prevent errors in our database. As permissible, we may also supplement the information you provide to us with demographic and other information (such as age or interest in photography) stored in third-party databases in order to make it more likely that marketing communications we send will be of interest to you.
How your personal information is used
Lexcycle collects your information in order to record, support
and facilitate
your participation in the activities you select. If you subscribe to or register for Products and Services, for example, the information is used to register your rights, if any, to technical support or other benefits that may be made available to registered users. As another example, if you enter a contest, information is collected to qualify the entry and to contact you regarding the contest or prize awards. Your personal information is also used to track customer preferences and keep you informed about product upgrades, special offers, and other products and services of Lexcycle and selected third parties unless you have opted not to receive such communications or such communications are prohibited by law.
Lexcycle may collect information about the use of the Products and Services and the Site, such as the number of downloads, types of Services used, how many users we receive daily, and the IP/Internet address of your computer. This information is collected in aggregate form, without identifying any user individually.
Lexcycle may use this aggregate, nonidentifying statistical data for improving the Site and the Products and Services, providing more relevant experiences to our customers and for statistical analysis.
Certain Products and Services may require you to use the most current version of such Product and Service or are offered in conjunction with other Products and Services, which you may or may not have already downloaded.
The Product and Service may automatically check to determine if you are using the most current version or have other Products and Services and through e-mail messages, pop-up boxes or similar mechanisms inform you if need to upgrade in order to use the Product and Service you have requested.
During this process, an IP address identifying your computer and the Product and Service version may be sent to a Web server, but system profile information is not transmitted nor are cookies used to store information.
Your choices with respect to personal information
Lexcycle recognizes and appreciates the importance of responsible use of information collected on the Site and in connection with the Products and Services. Lexcycle will respect your legal rights regarding access to and correction and deletion of your personal information. Lexcycle may communicate information to you regarding products, services, and special offers available from Lexcycle or selected third parties unless you have opted not to receive such communications or such communications are prohibited by law, although we may find it necessary to continue to communicate with you regarding your use of the Site and the Products and Services. Except in the particular circumstances described in this Privacy Policy, Lexcycle will not provide your name to other companies or organizations without your consent.
There are other instances in which Lexcycle may divulge your personal information, such as where required by law, regulation, or litigation. We may also disclose information about you if we determine that such disclosure should be made for reasons of national security, law enforcement, or other issues of public importance.
Protection of your personal information
The personal information that you provide in connection with registering yourself as a user of the Site or of the Products and Services is classified as Registration Information.
Registration Information is protected in several ways. Access by you to your Registration Information is available through a password and unique customer ID selected by you. This password is encrypted. We recommend that you do not divulge your password to anyone. In addition, your Registration Information resides on secure servers that only selected Lexcycle personnel and contractors have access to via password. Lexcycle encrypts your personal information and thereby strives to prevent unauthorized parties from viewing such information when it is transmitted to Lexcycle.
Personal information that you provide that does not constitute Registration Information also resides on secure servers and is accessible only to selected Lexcycle personnel and contractors via password. Since this information is not accessible online by you, you will not be asked to select a password in order to view or modify such information.
Please note that any information you post to a public bulletin board, blog or chat room, such as the Lexcycle User Forums (the "Forums"), is available to all persons accessing that location, and your e-mail address may also be posted on these venues. The information you share, including your email address, would then be available to all persons accessing these venues, and such information may be read, collected or used by others for any purpose, including sending you unsolicited messages. Lexcycle is not responsible for any information you elect to submit in these venues or the use of such information. In addition, you should be aware that the Forums offer a service in which subscribers are e-mailed a copy of all messages posted to the Forums on a particular topic. Consequently, if you post a message to the Forums, your e-mail address will be sent to those subscribers who have indicated an interest in the topic of your message.
Data not collected on this Site or in connection with the Products and Services
Personal information that is not collected on the Site or in connection with the Products and Services is not generally subject to this Privacy Policy. However, personal information submitted on physical product registration cards is classified as Registration Information and is subject to this Privacy Policy. This Privacy Policy also covers licensee information (such as contact name and address) provided in connection with Lexcycle's volume licensing program. If you wish to access and/or correct such information, please see instructions for doing so in the section entitled "Updating your personal information and privacy preferences."
Tracking, use of cookies, web beacons and similar devices
In order to improve our Products and Services and the Site and provide more convenient, relevant experiences to our customers, we and our vendors may use "cookies", “web beacons”, and similar devices to track your activities.
A cookie is small amount of data that is transferred to your browser by a web server and can only be read by the server that gave it to you. It functions as your identification card and enables Lexcycle to record your passwords, purchases, and preferences. It cannot be executed as code or deliver viruses. A web beacon is a small transparent gif image that is embedded in an HTML page or email used to track when the page or email has been viewed.
A similar device may be used by which a Product and Service may send data to a server when a set of user-initiated events occur such as the “Add to Cart” button is clicked. This device is similar to a cookie in that it tracks your visit and the data can only be read by the server that receives the data. It is different than a cookie in that it is not browser-based, may not function as an identification card, and does not store any data on your computer.
While Lexcycle uses cookies and similar devices to track your use of the Site and the Products and Services, such as the number of downloads, types of Products and Services used and downloaded, how many users we receive daily, and our web servers automatically log the IP/Internet address of your computer, Lexcycle does not generally use this information to identify you personally. However, if you expressly provide consent for the Site or the Product and Service to "remember" the unique identifier that you select when you register for various activities on the Site or the Products and Services, that unique identifier will be stored on a cookie on your computer and that unique identifier will be linked to your Registration Information.
As a result, your navigation path around the Site and the Products and Services will be tracked.
Some Products and Services allow the tracking of access to or use of Products and Services by users, as opposed to Lexcycle.
For example, certain Products and Services allow document authors to restrict access to documents, track access to or use of those documents, or involve communications and transmission of data over the Internet to verify the authenticity of documents, authors and recipients.
In many cases, this type of tracking will be obvious to you as a user of the Products and Services, and in others, the software and services license or terms of use, pop-up boxes, or email messages will inform you of these features and your options, such as disabling options.
Most browsers are initially set to accept cookies, and most Products and Services that include similar devices are typically initially activated to collect data. You can set your browser to notify you when you receive a cookie, giving you the chance to decide whether or not to accept it. (For some web pages that require an authorization, cookies are not optional. Users choosing not to accept cookies or similar devices will probably not be able to access those pages or the related Products and Services.) Information about non-cookie tracking devices and their features, including disabling options, are contained in the information materials provided with such Products and Services or on Site pages relating to such Products and Services.
Lexcycle also hires other companies to place our banner ads on other websites and where they are permitted to perform tracking and reporting activities ("third-party advertisement servers"). Aside from IP addresses, they do not collect personally identifiable information in doing this work for us, and we do not give any personally identifiable information to them. Third-party advertisement servers are subject to their own privacy policies. Lexcycle may also allow other companies to display advertisements on certain pages of the Site or within the Products and Services. If you click on these advertisements these companies may place a persistent cookie on your computer which will allow them to contact you directly. It is our policy to require these companies to provide accessible methods for you to disable these cookies, and should you have any complaint about the practices of any of these companies you should contact privacy-officer@lexcycle.com.
Privacy complaints
Lexcycle takes its users' privacy concerns seriously. If you believe that Lexcycle has not complied with this Privacy Policy with respect to your personal information, you may write to the Lexcycle Privacy Officer at the following address:
Lexcycle, Inc.
Privacy Officer/Customer Information
1412 SE 41st Ave
Portland, OR 97214
USA
Email:
privacy-officer@lexcycle.com.
If you provide Lexcycle with inconsistent privacy preferences (for example, by indicating on one occasion that third parties may contact you with marketing offers and indicating on another occasion that they may not), Lexcycle will endeavor to update your privacy preferences in a timely and accurate manner.
Also, please note that Lexcycle is not responsible for the content or privacy practices of non-Lexcycle websites to which this Site or any other Lexcycle website may link. You should review the privacy policy of such sites before using the sites.
About Us | Site Map | RSS Feeds | Media Info | Terms of Use | Privacy Policy
Copyright © 2009 Lexcycle, Inc. All rights reserved.
Active forum topics
iPhone Feature Requests
Bug report with Stanza 3.0 for iPhone 3GS
Stanza 1.9.1 Downgrade
How to get books from Ipod Stanza back to the PC?
What credit card # when using micropay?
Where do you do most of your reading with Stanza iPhone/iPod?:
Experimental Picture Book Capability Now Available in Stanza 2.1 for iPhone, iPod Touch
Restoring Stanza books from iTunes backup
6 More Books Now Available in the Random House Free Catalog on Stanza iPhone
How to Read Right to Left Languages in Stanza iPhone
Stanza has been selected by O'Reilly Media as a Best iPhone App
Wil Anderson's eBook Available for Free for Stanza iPhone / iPod Touch Users in Australia and NZ
Lexcycle has been acquired by Amazon.com!
24 Hours Only - Free Download of Orange Prize Shortlist Book for UK Stanza Users
Lexcycle at London Book Fair
more
Random FAQs
How do I save content to my Kindle?
How do I share books from Stanza Desktop with Stanza iPhone if I don't have a wireless network?
Can Stanza Desktop share with Stanza iPhone if I have my firewall enabled?
How do I change the title or author of my book when sharing it with Stanza iPhone?
Is the Online Catalog available for Stanza Desktop?
All FAQs
